<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Depression on jackpurrin&#39;s digital journal</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/depression/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Depression on jackpurrin&#39;s digital journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
      <managingEditor>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</managingEditor>
    
    
      <webMaster>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</webMaster>
    
    
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024-2025, jackpurrin.</copyright>
    
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:26:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
    
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/depression/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>my life feels fucked</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/p/my-life-feels-fucked/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:26:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/my-life-feels-fucked/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i really just feel like my life is not going to end well. i won&amp;rsquo;t be sucsuessful, i won&amp;rsquo;t be able to have what i want or need, and i wont be able to actually have a good life. i mean like i can&amp;rsquo;t get a job, i can barely get a good education, and i just can&amp;rsquo;t really be happy. i&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling to be happy and it&amp;rsquo;s taken it&amp;rsquo;s toll on me. i&amp;rsquo;ve been stressed to shit having to deal with summer school and stuff, i&amp;rsquo;ve felt really lonely lately, and i&amp;rsquo;ve been so bored.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;jobs&#34;&gt;jobs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i &lt;strong&gt;had&lt;/strong&gt; a passion for cybersecurity and programming, but it&amp;rsquo;s not worth it anymore. A.I. is taking over our economy and companies would rather pay for cheap robots than real humans. i love it and all, and before A.I. i wanted to go professional, make it my life and job! not for the money, just pure passion. slowly but surely, all of the jobs in that feild will be taken over. whole people&amp;rsquo;s lives have been ruined because A.I. took it over. gone for greed&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;education&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i really wanted to go to college, not a crazy ivy leauge school, but &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.asu.edu/&#34;&gt;ASU&lt;/a&gt;. this has been a problem for a while, so not a new one, but how will i ever go to college if i can&amp;rsquo;t afford the price? it ties back to the jobs, i can&amp;rsquo;t afford collge with a deadbeat job i&amp;rsquo;ll never even apply the education for.&#xA;don&amp;rsquo;t even get me started on grade school&amp;hellip; these gen-alpha kids and new freshmen are absolute pieces of shit! they treat their teachers like shit, they don&amp;rsquo;t learn, and they are super annoying. when i was a freshmen, even then most of the freshmen were assholes. it&amp;rsquo;s crazy to think that kids can act like that to teachers and people of authority.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;home&#34;&gt;home&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;house prices have been skyrocketing, and not just buying a house. renting something like an apartment is &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; expensive. i don&amp;rsquo;t want to live in my parents&amp;rsquo; house for very long. i want to get out but i just can&amp;rsquo;t. arizona used to be cheap but like everywhere else, it got expensive as fuck. i don&amp;rsquo;t mind living in an apartment but it&amp;rsquo;s just too expensive. i just can&amp;rsquo;t imagine how expensive it will be by the time where i&amp;rsquo;m old enough to move out. it&amp;rsquo;s not going to be great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-things&#34;&gt;other things&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;like politics. i absolutely hate politics, but from what i&amp;rsquo;ve heard, it does not sound like the USA is going to be a chill place to live in anymore. passing crazy bills that will be dangerous for the people, doing things that make america feel more like a dictatorship, and ruining our human rights. e.g. donald trump suing WSJ for making an article about the epstien stuff or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i mean like i don&amp;rsquo;t even know anymore. thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i&#39;m fine, i&#39;m just tired...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/p/im-fine-im-just-tired.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 20:07:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/p/im-fine-im-just-tired.../</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s hard to start a topic like this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-ive-been-feeling&#34;&gt;how i&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well that is kinda easy to start on.. i recently have been feeling a lot of ways. sad, burnt-out, tired, numb, irritated, upset, anxious and stressed. it&amp;rsquo;s bad. also, it is not just a new thing that i am feeling this way, been feeling this way for a long time. it first started around a month or two before i moved schools. but the reasons have changed for why i am feeling these ways. well, the deep underlying reason has not changed, but the contributors have changed. why then does not matter at this moment, but why now kinda does. or does it? am i just being silly, dumb, crazy?? i don&amp;rsquo;t really know. and i will not know for a really long time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;invalidation&#34;&gt;invalidation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i mean like, i just do not feel like my problems are real. i have been kind of gaslight into beliving my life is perfect, i am okay, nothing is wrong. but deep down, i really know something is not right. my family just makes it seem that my problems are not real. i hate talking to my mom about my problems. but one time i did, and i was talking about just how i felt mentally drained by the stuff happening at school. i breifly mentioned i feel anxious all of the time, andshe immeditely said &lt;code&gt;oh it is just high school drama, you will get over it evantually.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;another time was when i was talking about my boyfriend with my mom. i mentioned that he was getting the help he needed, and about the fact he at one point, practiced self harm. my mom said something like &lt;code&gt;oh it is just him being silly! he probobly was not hurting himself, just looking for attention. he feeds off of attention.&lt;/code&gt; WHY THE FUCK WOULD MY MOM SAY THAT?? well besides the point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mostly-why-i-feel-invalidated&#34;&gt;mostly why i feel invalidated&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so one night i was talking to my boyfriend, and i was not feeling good at all. he was trying to help me, and he told me to email one of his teachers. bear in mind, it was two in the morning. so i email the teacher and move about my night. i wake up, and it is like nine in the morning. my mom is waking me up, said &lt;code&gt;you do not need to be sleeping in until eleven like yesterday. especially with how late you were up last night.&lt;/code&gt; how did she know i was up so late? well, the pricipal of my school called my mom. i was not in any trouble, but my pricipal was worried about me. so my mom drags me into my backyard and tells me to sit down, she needed to talk to me about something. she made me try and talk about my problems. now i didn&amp;rsquo;t say everything, but i did slightly mention how i feel numb and do not feel happy. ever. and she just said it is hormones, just normal teenager things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-will-not-know-if-i-am-depressed&#34;&gt;i will not know if i am depressed&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well during that conversation with my mom, she brung up therapy. she said she did not wanna get me therapy. mainly because she did not want the therapists to just put me on anti-depressants and call it a day. she also said that most therapists are not qualified and just throw medication at you to get you away. they do not care about their patients, and just want money. she said that anti-depressants do not work anyways. when you take them, they sometimes work, and then when you are off of them, you wanna kill yourself. but i have heard of plenty of people i know who take anti-depressants that are just fine. here is what makes it even funnier, she said that when i am of leagal age, she would be willing to smoke weed with me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-i-feel&#34;&gt;how i feel&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i constantly feel sad. i have these mood swings and it bothers me. one minuite i am happy, the other i am really really sad.&#xA;i feel constantly anxious about everything. one thing that has been killing my anxiety is my relationship. i constantly feel like he is pushing me away and he might leave me. i do not feel our relationship is as intimate as before, and it has been killing me.&#xA;i feel stressed and burnt-out. my parents have been making me do all sorts of had things. i had to paint some walls today, then scrub the paint off of the baseboards. it was silly.&#xA;when i am anxious, i can also get easily irritated. so i have been getting upset over the smallest things :/&#xA;i feel super dysphoric. i wish i did not live my life, lived another. i will write about that later, &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me&#34;&gt;placeholder link&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;and so much more, but it is hard to write about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-it-has-affected-me&#34;&gt;how it has affected me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not feel motivated to do anything at all. i do not wanna play games with my friends, i do not wanna work on my website, i barely had the motivation to write this post. i was gonna write some posts on my music taste, my self identity problems (hint, i might be a femboyyyyy), and my forest post.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;it has affected my romantic relationship&amp;hellip; i am constantly feeling anxious that he might leave me and i feel like it has made our relationship less intimate and secure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not wanna leave my bed at all, fortunetly, i have to.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not wanna eat at all, when i eat i feel sick and i feel uncomfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not feel as smart as i used to be, so it may affect my grades in the future.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>