<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on jackpurrin&#39;s digital journal</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on jackpurrin&#39;s digital journal</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
      <managingEditor>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</managingEditor>
    
    
      <webMaster>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</webMaster>
    
    
    <copyright>Copyright © 2024-2025, jackpurrin.</copyright>
    
    
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:26:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
    
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>my life feels fucked</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/life/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jul 2025 22:26:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/life/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i really just feel like my life is not going to end well. i won&amp;rsquo;t be sucsuessful, i won&amp;rsquo;t be able to have what i want or need, and i wont be able to actually have a good life. i mean like i can&amp;rsquo;t get a job, i can barely get a good education, and i just can&amp;rsquo;t really be happy. i&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling to be happy and it&amp;rsquo;s taken it&amp;rsquo;s toll on me. i&amp;rsquo;ve been stressed to shit having to deal with summer school and stuff, i&amp;rsquo;ve felt really lonely lately, and i&amp;rsquo;ve been so bored.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;jobs&#34;&gt;jobs&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i &lt;strong&gt;had&lt;/strong&gt; a passion for cybersecurity and programming, but it&amp;rsquo;s not worth it anymore. A.I. is taking over our economy and companies would rather pay for cheap robots than real humans. i love it and all, and before A.I. i wanted to go professional, make it my life and job! not for the money, just pure passion. slowly but surely, all of the jobs in that feild will be taken over. whole people&amp;rsquo;s lives have been ruined because A.I. took it over. gone for greed&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;education&#34;&gt;education&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i really wanted to go to college, not a crazy ivy leauge school, but &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.asu.edu/&#34;&gt;ASU&lt;/a&gt;. this has been a problem for a while, so not a new one, but how will i ever go to college if i can&amp;rsquo;t afford the price? it ties back to the jobs, i can&amp;rsquo;t afford collge with a deadbeat job i&amp;rsquo;ll never even apply the education for.&#xA;don&amp;rsquo;t even get me started on grade school&amp;hellip; these gen-alpha kids and new freshmen are absolute pieces of shit! they treat their teachers like shit, they don&amp;rsquo;t learn, and they are super annoying. when i was a freshmen, even then most of the freshmen were assholes. it&amp;rsquo;s crazy to think that kids can act like that to teachers and people of authority.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;home&#34;&gt;home&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;house prices have been skyrocketing, and not just buying a house. renting something like an apartment is &lt;em&gt;so&lt;/em&gt; expensive. i don&amp;rsquo;t want to live in my parents&amp;rsquo; house for very long. i want to get out but i just can&amp;rsquo;t. arizona used to be cheap but like everywhere else, it got expensive as fuck. i don&amp;rsquo;t mind living in an apartment but it&amp;rsquo;s just too expensive. i just can&amp;rsquo;t imagine how expensive it will be by the time where i&amp;rsquo;m old enough to move out. it&amp;rsquo;s not going to be great.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;other-things&#34;&gt;other things&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;like politics. i absolutely hate politics, but from what i&amp;rsquo;ve heard, it does not sound like the USA is going to be a chill place to live in anymore. passing crazy bills that will be dangerous for the people, doing things that make america feel more like a dictatorship, and ruining our human rights. e.g. donald trump suing WSJ for making an article about the epstien stuff or whatever.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i mean like i don&amp;rsquo;t even know anymore. thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i&#39;m fine, i&#39;m just tired...</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 20:07:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/depression/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;it&amp;rsquo;s hard to start a topic like this.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-ive-been-feeling&#34;&gt;how i&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well that is kinda easy to start on.. i recently have been feeling a lot of ways. sad, burnt-out, tired, numb, irritated, upset, anxious and stressed. it&amp;rsquo;s bad. also, it is not just a new thing that i am feeling this way, been feeling this way for a long time. it first started around a month or two before i moved schools. but the reasons have changed for why i am feeling these ways. well, the deep underlying reason has not changed, but the contributors have changed. why then does not matter at this moment, but why now kinda does. or does it? am i just being silly, dumb, crazy?? i don&amp;rsquo;t really know. and i will not know for a really long time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;invalidation&#34;&gt;invalidation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i mean like, i just do not feel like my problems are real. i have been kind of gaslight into beliving my life is perfect, i am okay, nothing is wrong. but deep down, i really know something is not right. my family just makes it seem that my problems are not real. i hate talking to my mom about my problems. but one time i did, and i was talking about just how i felt mentally drained by the stuff happening at school. i breifly mentioned i feel anxious all of the time, andshe immeditely said &lt;code&gt;oh it is just high school drama, you will get over it evantually.&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;another time was when i was talking about my boyfriend with my mom. i mentioned that he was getting the help he needed, and about the fact he at one point, practiced self harm. my mom said something like &lt;code&gt;oh it is just him being silly! he probobly was not hurting himself, just looking for attention. he feeds off of attention.&lt;/code&gt; WHY THE FUCK WOULD MY MOM SAY THAT?? well besides the point.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mostly-why-i-feel-invalidated&#34;&gt;mostly why i feel invalidated&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so one night i was talking to my boyfriend, and i was not feeling good at all. he was trying to help me, and he told me to email one of his teachers. bear in mind, it was two in the morning. so i email the teacher and move about my night. i wake up, and it is like nine in the morning. my mom is waking me up, said &lt;code&gt;you do not need to be sleeping in until eleven like yesterday. especially with how late you were up last night.&lt;/code&gt; how did she know i was up so late? well, the pricipal of my school called my mom. i was not in any trouble, but my pricipal was worried about me. so my mom drags me into my backyard and tells me to sit down, she needed to talk to me about something. she made me try and talk about my problems. now i didn&amp;rsquo;t say everything, but i did slightly mention how i feel numb and do not feel happy. ever. and she just said it is hormones, just normal teenager things.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-will-not-know-if-i-am-depressed&#34;&gt;i will not know if i am depressed&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well during that conversation with my mom, she brung up therapy. she said she did not wanna get me therapy. mainly because she did not want the therapists to just put me on anti-depressants and call it a day. she also said that most therapists are not qualified and just throw medication at you to get you away. they do not care about their patients, and just want money. she said that anti-depressants do not work anyways. when you take them, they sometimes work, and then when you are off of them, you wanna kill yourself. but i have heard of plenty of people i know who take anti-depressants that are just fine. here is what makes it even funnier, she said that when i am of leagal age, she would be willing to smoke weed with me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-i-feel&#34;&gt;how i feel&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i constantly feel sad. i have these mood swings and it bothers me. one minuite i am happy, the other i am really really sad.&#xA;i feel constantly anxious about everything. one thing that has been killing my anxiety is my relationship. i constantly feel like he is pushing me away and he might leave me. i do not feel our relationship is as intimate as before, and it has been killing me.&#xA;i feel stressed and burnt-out. my parents have been making me do all sorts of had things. i had to paint some walls today, then scrub the paint off of the baseboards. it was silly.&#xA;when i am anxious, i can also get easily irritated. so i have been getting upset over the smallest things :/&#xA;i feel super dysphoric. i wish i did not live my life, lived another. i will write about that later, &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me&#34;&gt;placeholder link&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;and so much more, but it is hard to write about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-it-has-affected-me&#34;&gt;how it has affected me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not feel motivated to do anything at all. i do not wanna play games with my friends, i do not wanna work on my website, i barely had the motivation to write this post. i was gonna write some posts on my music taste, my self identity problems (hint, i might be a femboyyyyy), and my forest post.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;it has affected my romantic relationship&amp;hellip; i am constantly feeling anxious that he might leave me and i feel like it has made our relationship less intimate and secure.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not wanna leave my bed at all, fortunetly, i have to.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not wanna eat at all, when i eat i feel sick and i feel uncomfortable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i do not feel as smart as i used to be, so it may affect my grades in the future.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>summer is going to be horrible</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/summer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 09:43:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/summer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;well summer break started this thursday! i mean like some good things happened, read about it &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me/posts/insanity&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but it&amp;rsquo;s also slow as hell.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;school&#34;&gt;school&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well before summer break, i had stuff to do and things to be exited for in the day. i had friends to hang out with, i had classes to look forward to, it was something to pass the time. i was not just sitting down at my computer all day, doing nothing. it made me a more active person. i have to walk to school, and on top off that i had pe so there was plenty of things that kept my step count above 10 thousand. (yes, i will prove it if you do not belive me) i will admit though, school was not all sunshine and rainbows though. if i am being honest, it had made my mental state 100 times worse. of course, i had the constant stress and anxiety caused by some people. for example, this girl i will call orange, stirred up constant drama and could never seem to find a end to her fucking problems. so she just took it out on us. i also had the stress of school work. i am a gifted student, i do well in school! turns out one of my favorite subjects was the one that was the most stressful unfortunately. my ela teacher gave me so much work, and i have been dealing with burnout from mental problems, so it was hard to do the amount of work she gave me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;an-escape&#34;&gt;an escape&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;school was also an escape from home. some of the things it gave me an escape from&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;brother being an asshole&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i walk on eggshells at home. my stepdad can get aggressive at times. with no warning.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;i have a lot of work to do at home, like constant dishes&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;literally an escape. my parents do not usually take us out of the house, so school was my way to leave.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;an escape from the bordem of being home. days blur together, there is not much to do at home.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;younger-times&#34;&gt;younger times&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;when i was younger, i never had problems with the house being boring. partly because when i was younger, i had shows to watch, i had games i liked to play, and i was also able to go to my dad&amp;rsquo;s house. his house actually had fun things to do that were not screens. and also he had cats, and as you could guess, i  love cats. plenty of things to do! but because of unfortunate circumstances, i do not see my dad much anymore, i do not find joy in playing many games, and my mom cancelled all of her subscriptions because she wanted DVDs instead. so no anime 😿.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;winter-break&#34;&gt;winter break&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;winter break is relevant because it shows what could happen to me during summer break. winter break was two weeks long. summer break is usually ten weeks long. so therefore, the effects would be five times stronger. i was lonely, i was numb, and i was unfortunately suicidal. i had no one to hang out with, i had nothing to do, i felt like my life had no meaning. i felt like i was wasting my time doing literally nothing. i could have been doing so much more, like hanging out with friends at the mall, or trying to make friends at public places like parks. but my parents would not have done that. but winter break kinda changed me for the better. at my old school i was kinda the quiet kid, but i knew a couple kids. after that i became a bit more social. but some of those mental problems kind of stuck with me after winter break.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;this-summer&#34;&gt;this summer&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;even though it only has been a couple of days, it has been boring. but some good things happened like i mentioned earlier. this summer break i have one friend i can hang out with though! {insert is github if he is okay with it}. i have not really had much to do at all. i do have some sort of goals for the summer but they feel so out of reach.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;try and go on a walk every day&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;read more, i like gay romance (or just straight romance) 😊&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;convince my mom to let me go to the library more&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;try and learn the guitar&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;try and learn to draw&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;learn photogrophy and videography&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;fix my sleep schedule&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;find a way to get some cash&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;write more!!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;do some more cooking&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;and convince my mother to take us to california&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mental-health&#34;&gt;mental health&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i just really hope that my mental health wont degrade again. it is already at a bad spot, constant anxiety, stress, not feeling happy much, etc. and i am scared summer might just make it worse. i have to push my mom to let us do things, and my mom is trying to get a new job (got laid off a while ago) so she might not even have time to do stuff. both stepdad and mom should be employed so no parents can really do much. being isolated much is not good, but hopefully i can have a friend over sometimes. i have goals to keep myself occupied but i do not know how long those should last and it may just lead me to being bored again and i already feel like i am wasting so much time. really though, what am i doing? i would never commit but like thoughts sometimes come by and it scared the living shit out of me. i just hope soon i can get the help i need and summer will be over quickly. then i can have a purpouse again.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well thanks for reading, leave a reaction and comment to show your support! or just leave some feedback!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>love is making me insane :3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/insanity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 23:30:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/insanity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i really do not know how to start this. it is kinda funny to think just two days ago i was writing about &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me/posts/lovesick/&#34;&gt;how lovesick i am&lt;/a&gt;. how silly :/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-were-still-friends&#34;&gt;we were still friends&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so after me and cuddles broke up, we were still friends. you can read more about the breakup &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me/posts/heartbreak/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. it was hella awkward being friends tho. it felt off to be around him. the best way i can describe how i felt when i saw him was &lt;code&gt;jealous&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;lovesick&lt;/code&gt;. hours go by, i did not get over him. days go by. hell even like two weeks went by and i still was not over him. we broke up around the end of the school year, and school ended today actually! so i hoped it would be easier to get over him over the summer. especially because i believed i was never going to see him again because he were moving to another school. it was also kinda sad to think about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-was-still-in-love-and-so-was-he&#34;&gt;i was still in love, and so was he.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;for some context, a week or two after the breakup, we were talking and he said he regretted breaking up with me. he said he wanted to stay reserved for me while he still went to his new school. he also admitted to still be loving me. i also still loved him. that sounded nice and all but i have serious trust issues. so i asked what was the ratio between how much he wanted to be with me and how much of it was just to make me happy. he said 50/50. so i said it would just be better to stay as friends. but we both still loved each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;summer-break&#34;&gt;summer break&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so like i said earlier, summer break started today. even though it has only been a day, summer break has been boring as hell. he was the only person keeping my sanity in check though. he was pretty much the only person i texted, other than like one or two friends. today while i was in the shower, i was thinking about what if cuddles did not move schools? and so after that shower i was talking to cuddles about being lovesick and shit. we were both lovesick and was just talking about it. well he broke some awesome news. good news for me, and good news for him.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;awesome-news&#34;&gt;awesome news&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the same day cuddles said he would never see me or any of his friends again because he was moving schools is the same day he the said that his mom was letting him stay at my school instead of the one he was gonna move to!!! and we were already talking about our relationship, and he says something that catches me so off guard. we were talking about some stuff, like some relationship retrospective. during that conversation he brung up that his mom is letting him stay at my school. that changed our conversation wildly. well we kept talking, and instead of saying &lt;code&gt;okay&lt;/code&gt; or something like that, he said &lt;code&gt;okay my dear&lt;/code&gt;. i immediately am thinking &lt;code&gt;oh my fucking god. no fucking way he said that.&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;am i dreaming? is this real?&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;is he saying what i think he is saying? are we dating again?!?!?!&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-ask&#34;&gt;i ask&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i asked him if he wanted to stay reserved for me for a little while, and he says &lt;code&gt;it is just staying reserved&lt;/code&gt;. when i asked about being resevred, i also mentioned being scared to say something. the thing in question was &lt;code&gt;so since you said **okay my dear** it got me thinking that you were hinting at dating me again&lt;/code&gt;. and his response to that was &lt;code&gt;not officaly.&lt;/code&gt;. i am so fucking excitedddd!!! also, the reason why i got so amped up about him calling me dear is because while we were dating, he knew my favorite name to be called was &lt;code&gt;my dear&lt;/code&gt; behind &lt;code&gt;good boy&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-he-has-been-treating-me&#34;&gt;how he has been treating me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well like, he has been treating me like were actually dating, and over the summer i hope we will actually be offically be dating!! like yeah we have both been using the pet names, but he has also been saying things like how much he wants to kiss me, and like how much he desires my cuddles. i will admit i have been saying the same stuff back, but it is not like it is bad that we have been saying that stuff. it just seems like we are offically dating.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;mistakes&#34;&gt;mistakes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i hope we will have learned from our mistakes, the both of us. i need to learn to be less pushy, and he also needed to learn to communicate better. if he had communicated how he was feeling about our realtionship when he did not feel like he was mentally stable enough to be in a realtionshp, we could have talked it out. he did not feel stable enough to make sure i felt seen and got what i wanted from him. if he told me that, i would have asked for less, and it would have been okay with me! becase true love is making sacrifcies.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well yeah, that is pretty much it. thanks for reading, and make sure to leave a reaction/comment below so i can see your guy&amp;rsquo;s feedback!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i&#39;ve fallen lovesick</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/lovesick/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 May 2025 15:15:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/lovesick/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;being in love is awesome. you finally found the person you love, and then you pour your heart, soul, time, and life into them. and then it ends. the person breaks up with you. it hurts a lot and i wrote about it &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me/posts/heartbreak/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;it-hurts-metaphorically&#34;&gt;it hurts, metaphorically&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but eventually, you will get the big pain out of the way. the best way to describe it metaphorically is a stab. you get stabbed by a knife, and it hurts like hell. but that big pain does not last long, because after the knife (the problem/your now ex) is removed from you, it leaves a mark, and bleeds. the bleeding is what i am feeling. and i think it is like being lovesick.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-has-it-affected-me&#34;&gt;how has it affected me?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the constant pain has made my life so much more worse. i have had mental issues for a while, before i started dating him. but it only made them worse. he was the person i could step to when i needed to talk about something that was on my mind. like i have friends and all, and i do talk to them, but he was the person i let the most out to because i was the most comfortable around him. it would be weird to just start yapping about my deeper mental issues to one of my friends. he helped calm me down when i was anxious or stressed. take, for example, my choir concert. i was so stressed and anxious because i did not wanna sing and it was in front of a lot of people. but he helped me out so much, made me so calm and confident that i was going to be okay. and i did great!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-have-to-confess&#34;&gt;i have to confess&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i hate to admit this, but really, i am touch starved. before i dated him, i had not had a hug in a couple years. i kinda forgot hugs exist. and then hugs became a daily thing. or i just really liked having his hand on my back, his touch felt so good. i have a body pillow, and i cuddle with it every night. cuddling helped me fall asleep. and i had him in mind because i wanted to cuddle him so bad!! but that unfortunately never happened. and it sucks because now when i cuddle my body pillow, i have no one to wish to cuddle or think about. i loved it when his head was on my chest, it made me so happy. even on days i had struggles being happy, his head on my chest always helped. also having that person where i could put my hands on them without it being weird or uncomfortable was nice. nothing &lt;em&gt;freaky&lt;/em&gt; but just like having a place to put my hands was nice.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;ive-felt-lonely-my-whole-life&#34;&gt;i&amp;rsquo;ve felt lonely my whole life&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i have always been a lonely person. i have friends and all, but like i have never had anyone super close. and for the first semester of my high school year, i did not really have close friends. a classmate here and there, but no one notable. and so having someone like my ex to just be with, helped me feel less lonely. before i dated him, i would never think of myself as a necessarily lonely person, but you never knew what you lost until you lose it. and now he is gone, i truly have realized how lonely i really am. i will admit tho, i have a somewhat close friend that i do not think i will lose for a while, but like, it is not what i am looking for.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;we-could-relate&#34;&gt;we could relate&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;you know, me and him had similar struggles. he also had mental issues (the reason why we broke up, read more &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me/posts/heartbreak/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;), and so did i. we both do not have the greatest parents, we both had a lot in common. so it was nice to have someone to relate to! being able to be like, &lt;code&gt;oh man jeez, my step-dad is mad and he has been yelling lately&lt;/code&gt; and having him be like &lt;code&gt;oh man that sucks, i know how it feels, i wish you were not having to deal with that, it sucks..&lt;/code&gt; was nice. but now i will not have that for a good while. or just be able to talk about something in common, like we both liked the forest more than the beach. it was nice to just be able to talk without having to think too hard about what we should talk about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-going-to-miss-this&#34;&gt;i&amp;rsquo;m going to miss this&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;but now it is gone, and i am really gonna miss it for a while. i will give him credit where it is due tho, he did teach me a lot about myself and a lot about relationships. he also gave a real purpouse in life, someone that i could be there for, someone i could give my time to. but the pros barely outweigh the cons.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;code&gt;i got all the time in the world, don&#39;t you want some of that?&lt;/code&gt; - &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UZUD9B440w0&#34;&gt;Bahamas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well that&amp;rsquo;s pretty much that&amp;rsquo;s on my mind that i can think of, thanks for reading, and leave a comment or reaction below so i can hear your feedback please!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>he broke my heart</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/heartbreak/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/heartbreak/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;i can&amp;rsquo;t stop crying. heartbreak actually sucks. especially when it feels like your relationship was a lie.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well yeah, he broke up with me and it sucks so bad. he made promise after promise, but lie after lie. he even broke up with me in the worst way possible, pushing me away. let&amp;rsquo;s step back, and get some context first.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;some-context&#34;&gt;some context&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so i&amp;rsquo;ve been on edge about our relationship for a bit before we broke up. read some about that &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me/posts/important/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. he kept saying things like, &lt;code&gt;oh yeah, i&#39;ll braid your hair on tuesday&lt;/code&gt; then tuesday comes. but it doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen. and the loop continues, &lt;code&gt;i&#39;ll give you a kiss in the morning&lt;/code&gt;, but no kiss. time and time went on, and we&amp;rsquo;ve not been on the thickest ice. constant drama from one person or another causing stress on the both of us, and our relationship. well the night before he broke up with me, we were talking about our relationship. i asked &lt;code&gt;do you wanna maintain this realtionship, and do you think it&#39;s a good idea?&lt;/code&gt; and he said yes to both. he even promise not to be leaving me any time soon! so it seemed to be going okay. you know how i mentioned the hair thing? well that night too, he said he&amp;rsquo;d do my hair during a class period, rti. rti you&amp;rsquo;re able to choose what class you wanna go to, so he said that night he&amp;rsquo;d go to my rti! well the night passes by, and in the morning he says &lt;code&gt;well actually, i can&#39;t go to your rti, i gotta to go another period and i can&#39;t switch it.&lt;/code&gt; that made me a bit sad, but it was whatever. during rti, we were also emailing and they were saying stuff like how much they missed me and how much he loved me. okay, cool! it seemed our relationship was alright!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;one-hint-that-it-was-coming&#34;&gt;one hint that it was coming&amp;hellip;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;during rti, he said he&amp;rsquo;d do my hair during lunch. so the day passes, and it comes to lunch time. i usually follow him to get lunch with him even though i bring my own lunch. well today, he grabs his stuff (unusal for him) and he tells me to stay where i was, because he was going to a teacher after getting lunch. so that kinda hurt. then he left. and all of his friends followed. leaving me to sit by myself. and so i had a panic/anxiety attack. i started pacing around a building, and i can hear my ex having plenty of fun with his friends so i started crying. while i was pacing, i encountred one of my friends, he usually doesn&amp;rsquo;t eat lunch with us, so he roams. ofc i tell him what just happened. after that i go to my school&amp;rsquo;s student support staff and talk to someone about it. during that time, that friend who i talked to yelled at my ex, which i&amp;rsquo;m sure didn&amp;rsquo;t help :/&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-last-period-of-the-day&#34;&gt;the last period of the day&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;the day passes by until the last period, sixth period. which i usually have with my ex, so i planned on talking to him during that period. but they weren&amp;rsquo;t there. so i went to student support again, so i can talk about calming myself because i was having an anxiety attack again. guess who i see in the office? he wouldn&amp;rsquo;t look at me, and he was dead silent. he was playing a game on his phone. and also one of his friends was in there. so his friend pulled me out of the room. and she told me that my ex was breaking up with me. i cried so fucking hard, like so hard. i talked to the student support guy, my ex did and stuff. the school day ends and i walk home crying my ass off.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-actual-breakup-from-him&#34;&gt;the actual breakup from him&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well when i get home, my ex emails me trying to tell me he&amp;rsquo;s breaking up with me. he&amp;rsquo;s breaking up because he&amp;rsquo;s not mentally stable enough. he didn&amp;rsquo;t wanna tell me he was done because he was scared i was gonna hurt or kill myself. so i don&amp;rsquo;t really know how long he wanted to break up with me. i ask him how long he wanted to break up with me, and he said since the night before. so he lied to me about wanting to be in a relationship?? on top of that kept adding promises he&amp;rsquo;d never actually keep? like that felt so shitty it&amp;rsquo;s hard to describe. why didn&amp;rsquo;t he tell me what he was feeling and use proper communication? because if he actually talked to me about it, and said something, we could have fixed the problem. he later said that the relationship was adding too much stress on his life, he didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like he was good enough for me. i coulda just asked for less in our relationship. after all, one of the ways to show true love is to make sacrifices right?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well that&amp;rsquo;s all i wanted to say, and am able to write. writing this made me feel like i&amp;rsquo;m having an anxiety attack. thanks for reading, and leave a reaction or a comment below so i can see your feedback!!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>i don&#39;t feel important</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/important/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2025 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/important/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;y&amp;rsquo;know how it feels when you don&amp;rsquo;t feel like you&amp;rsquo;re important to someome signifigant? that&amp;rsquo;s how i&amp;rsquo;m feeling. it sucks, like a lot.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;who-am-i-even-talking-about&#34;&gt;who am i even talking about?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so i&amp;rsquo;ve been dating this guy for around 3 months now. let&amp;rsquo;s call him &lt;code&gt;cuddles&lt;/code&gt; because he loves cuddles 😖 . cuddles is the same person i wrote about &lt;a href=&#34;https://log.jackpurrin.me/posts/love/&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, but he&amp;rsquo;s transgender (ftm). just said that for some context. recently, one of cuddles&amp;rsquo; friends has been dealing with some tough shit. let&amp;rsquo;s call this person &lt;code&gt;orange&lt;/code&gt; cuz they have orange hair. orange&amp;rsquo;s boyfriend is graduating high school and is moving on to college. she&amp;rsquo;s worried that his boyfriend is gonna get really high and forget she exists and fuck someome. so she&amp;rsquo;s been scared to break up with him. well, she&amp;rsquo;s been all up in my cuddles&amp;rsquo; ass and it&amp;rsquo;s been&amp;hellip; intresting to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;promises&#34;&gt;promises&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;cuddles said that they would give me a five minuite hug yesterday. he said he would do it during our lunch break. also in the morning before they came to school, we were emailing. it was rainy outside and i asked if they wanted a kiss. i wanted to know if a kiss in the rain hits different. so he get to school. he say hi to me and the first thing they do is go to orange and discuss the drama. her and cuddles litterally ran away, and it seemed really embarrasing to follow my cuddles. i evantaully do because cuddles orange were getting breakfast. that kinda hurt that cuddles tried to leave without me, but whatever. other things would hurt more today.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-kiss&#34;&gt;the kiss?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;so the time rolls around for the kiss. we do our normal. we hug and i was about to kiss him. well that doesn&amp;rsquo;t happen, they zip away. so that kinda sucked. i emailed him about it later if they were really comfortable with a kiss. he said yes, so i asked if he wanted to get a kiss after one of our classes when we see each other. he say &lt;code&gt;sure!&lt;/code&gt;.  that class rolls around, and it ends. same ritual, walk to class, get a hug, and lean in for a kiss. well again, that didn&amp;rsquo;t happen. orange was busy surrounding cuddles with her drama and it just got in the way. so i emailed again, &lt;code&gt;are you sure you&#39;re really comfortable with a kiss?&lt;/code&gt;. but no response this time. i figured class got in the way.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-walk&#34;&gt;the walk&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well my math class passes by, and it&amp;rsquo;s time to walk sammy to thier biology class. so i walk them. after i take them to class, i usually hug them. there&amp;rsquo;s three bells at our school, end of class, get to class, and late bell. well the second bell rings during our hug. a hug that lasted a total of one second. they zip to class and i yell &lt;code&gt;you have 3 minutes left!&lt;/code&gt;. but they didn&amp;rsquo;t hear me. whatever.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;lunch-time&#34;&gt;lunch time!!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i go to my class, and it passes. slowly of course, but passes. it was lunch time! finally, time for a big and long hug! lunch ends at like 1:15. so we do normal lunch things, but the whole entire time, cuddles was again absorbed by orange&amp;rsquo;s bullshit. i ask him at 1, &lt;code&gt;hey are you still up for the five min hug?&lt;/code&gt; he say yeah. he don&amp;rsquo;t reach in for a hug, but i assume we&amp;rsquo;ll do it in a sec. 1 min passes, then two, then 5, then 10. i ask him again, &lt;code&gt;do you want a hug?&lt;/code&gt; and they say &lt;code&gt;no&lt;/code&gt;. what? so i didn&amp;rsquo;t get that hug i was promised.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;time-is-slowww&#34;&gt;time is slowww&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;after that, i go to my next class. it passes, that one is without cuddles. well the next occcurs, and it the class at the end of the day. i have that one with cuddles! well the entire class long, he were sucked into a conversation with someone else. all class long. it absolutely fucking sucked.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;end-of-the-day&#34;&gt;end of the day&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;class ends and i usually walk cuddles to his bus. i walk home so it usually isn&amp;rsquo;t a big deal. orange appears out of the blue and again, surrounds cuddles. i try my best to get a good hug from cuddles, and maybe that kiss? i mean the hug was alright but it didn&amp;rsquo;t feel that great. and again, he didn&amp;rsquo;t kiss me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i don&amp;rsquo;t know what to do anymore. this just sucks and i hate it. and i feel selfish to ask for some attention or to take away cuddles from what they consider more important for just some time with me and him.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well that&amp;rsquo;s my story of my day, thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>am i good enough?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/enough/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 18:00:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/enough/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;lately, i&amp;rsquo;ve been feeling like i&amp;rsquo;m not good enough. i don&amp;rsquo;t feel like i&amp;rsquo;ve been a good person at all.&#xA;i&amp;rsquo;ve also been thinking that my boyfriend doesn&amp;rsquo;t actually like me and stuff. i feel like i&amp;rsquo;ve been pushed away kinda.&#xA;i feel like my boyfriend would rather hang out with other people, and i&amp;rsquo;m scared that in the future they&amp;rsquo;re just gonna love someone more.  i get scared that our relationship isn&amp;rsquo;t going to last because they do things like simp over Call of Duty characters and people from bands. it makes me scared that one day someone will just come along in his life, and he will love them more.&#xA;or the time during our lunch break in school, he kinda ignored me because he wanted to hang out with his other friends. i sometimes feel like i&amp;rsquo;m just a side person.&#xA;he keeps just leaving for long times and doesn&amp;rsquo;t even tell me that they gotta go before they leave. i feel like he just is trying to run away from me.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>love is awesome</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2025 21:00:00 -0700</pubDate><author>me@jackpurrin.me (jackpurrin)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;omfg i’m so in love, i cannot even begin to describe it. alright lets back up and get some lore now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;i started to go to this new school because my brother got kicked outa my old school, and it’s been alright. there has been alot of pain from moving schools because the schedules were widely different. this led me to be stuck in choir even though i wish not to be in choir.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;choir is fun though! i do kinda enjoy the class even though i’m not a singer. it has made me expand my personal boundaries and the teacher is awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;some joys choir has gave me was a boy named shane. he’s in “shane” (sorry i won’t make dumb jokes i stole again.) but pretty chill. he kidnapped me and dragged me into robotics club. robotics is quite awseome and actually this saturday i have a competition to go to for robotics.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;speaking of meeting new kids, i fell in love. this girl, no names (i don’t wanna leak her name!), has my heart. she is so beautiful, and has an awesome personality. i can’t stop thinking about her, and it might just be driving me nuts. i have never dated a girl in my life 😭 so this is very new to me. she doesn’t know i like her and i’m scared to tell her or something. another thing i’m scared about is rejection. if she rejects me will i still be able to be friends? is it gonna be to embarrsing to just be friends?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;ughhh i dunno!!!! like i said before i’ve never dated a girl in my life so like i’m still a newbie. how do i date people y’know? how do i be a romantic person, or be a good boyfriend? why am i such an anxious person? it kills meeeeee. she’s pan so that’s cool. she makes me want to be a way better person too. she makes me feel like i have to break dumb and old habits, be funnier, and have a generally better personality.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;something embarrassing happened the other day. she was talking to me and i had full interest but i was so scared that i was gonna screw up to the point where i kept looking around the room instead of her 𝓫𝓮𝓪𝓾𝓽𝓲𝓯𝓾𝓵 eyes. i feel so shitty, and i dunno if she cared or not. my heart races when i’m around her and my heart is racing just writing this too. please help.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;she’s perfect, but in a imperfect way. everybody has their imperfections, but she is special as her imperfections make her perfect. i feel like i’m gonna cry now.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;well i dunno, and thanks for reading. &lt;a href=&#34;https://uquiz.com/quiz/w6OPts/what-color-are-you?p=3651636&#34;&gt;here&amp;rsquo;s a link.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>